Do you have a business brain?
你有商业头脑吗？
Are you always looking for the next great idea?
你总是在寻找下一个伟大的创意吗？
Maybe, like me, you might feel that starting a new company is something you do later in life when you have more experience.
也许，和我一样，你可能会觉得创办一家新公司是等你年纪大一些、有了更多经验之后才会做的事情。
But that's not always the case.
但情况并不总是这样。
While some of us may feel young adulthood is a time of tentatively finding our place in the world, sleeping late and partying hard, others are already on a path to great business success.
虽然我们中的一些人可能觉得青年时期是一个试探性地在世界上找到自己位置的时期，会睡懒觉、尽情聚会，但其他人已经走上了商业成功的道路。
Take the founder of Microsoft, Bill Gates, who started his company as a young university student at Harvard in the US.
以微软的创始人比尔·盖茨为例，他在美国哈佛大学还是一名年轻大学生的时候就创办了自己的公司。
There are many other examples of young entrepreneurs who have become hugely successful, proving that there's no minimum age to becoming top dog.
还有很多其他年轻企业家取得巨大成功的例子，证明成为佼佼者并没有最低年龄限制。
But to be the next business executive requires effort.
但是要成为下一位商业高管需要付出努力。
You need to acquire a keen mind and good business acumen and above all, you need enthusiasm.
你需要拥有聪明的头脑和良好的商业敏锐度，最重要的是，你需要有热情。
Starting a new business comes with an element of risk but if you are able to spot the next big idea, it's probably worth giving it a try.
创办一家新企业伴随着一定的风险，但如果你能够发现下一个伟大的创意，也许值得试一试。
Jessica Rose owns a jewellery making business and admits that "when I first started I had no business training whatsoever... but I kind of woke up one day and thought I'd really love to be a jewellery designer."
杰西卡·罗斯拥有一家珠宝制作企业，她承认：“我刚开始的时候没有接受过任何商业培训……但有一天我意识到，我真的很想成为一名珠宝设计师。”
She went on to be a successful young entrepreneur.
后来她成为了一名成功的年轻企业家。
Being young and in business does have its drawbacks; you may worry you have nothing to bring to the table and that the people who work for you tend to be older and wiser.
年轻且从事商业确实有它的缺点；你可能会担心自己没有什么可以提供出来的，而且为你工作的人往往年龄更大、更有智慧。
That's what young British entrepreneur Suleman Sacranie found.
这就是英国年轻企业家苏莱曼·萨克拉尼所发现的。
He started his third business whilst studying chemistry at university.
他在大学学习化学的时候创办了自己的第三家企业。
He says "now I've got two additional directors who have grey hair" but when they first started he says he "could tell they were thinking in the back of their heads, 'I've got a kid sitting in front of me.'"
他说：“现在我有两位头发花白的新董事”，但当他们刚开始的时候，他说他“能感觉到他们在心里想，‘我面前坐着一个毛头小子’。”
You may think setting up a new start-up is easier said than done.
你可能认为创办一家新的初创企业说起来容易做起来难。
As well as ideas, you need financial backing and expert guidance.
除了创意之外，你还需要资金支持和专家指导。
But if you're studying hard at university and don't have the desire to go into business and make your fortune, keep on studying — an education is priceless!
但是如果你在大学里努力学习，并且没有进入商业领域发财的愿望，那就继续学习吧——教育是无价的！